[Music]
Scroll down the feed. It's a circus
every day. Opinions over evidence. No
one cares what experts say. Shouting
matches everywhere except black pride.
Delusions of currency logic set aside.
We've all suspect for reason. Let
arrogance ignite
entertainment over truth. It's ignorance
in the light.
[Music]
Societies in free deceased. We celebrate
the loudest while intelligence decreases
power now. Stupidity is a trend.
Watching as our culture takes a no to
the end. Hey, hey, hey.
Jump it down.
[Music]
Headline stream with nonsense facts
don't matter anymore. Conspiracy
theories sell. Well, truth gets you on
the door. Experts are discredited. 146
center stage. Welcome to the kingdom
where the jester is a sage. We're
trading wisdom for clicks and tell just
for likes
breeding generations of mind that never
think twice. Societies every day to see.
We celebrate the loudest while
intelligence decreed
power. Now stupidity is a trend. Once
again our culture takes unknown to the
end. Hey, hey, hey.
Don't it down, dumb it down.
[Music]
[Applause]